{
    "id": "7f0ff0fd0b5945fdbc583f950e5c3bd5",
    "title": "Already, Still Or Yet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b9dd60868b74454389361e34ef699169",
            "title": "Already, Still Or Yet",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Is supper ready ...............................?",
                    "description": "In questions yet is used to ask whether something expected has happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have .................................. to hear from them.",
                    "description": "Yet is used before a to-infinitive to suggest that something has not happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "still",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They have ..................................... made an offer.",
                    "description": "Already refers to the present or past. It is used to suggest that something happened sooner than expected.",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "still",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ................................. to start working on the new project.",
                    "description": "Yet is used before a to-infinitive to suggest that something has not happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are ................................ waiting.",
                    "description": "Still is used to say that something is in the present and it has not finished.",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The university is ...................................... to publish the results.",
                    "description": "Yet is used before a to-infinitive to suggest that something has not happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ................................... raining.",
                    "description": "Still is used to say that something is in the present and it has not finished.",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The postman has ..................................... been.",
                    "description": "Already refers to the present or past. It is used to suggest that something happened sooner than expected.",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "still",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Has the postman come ........................................?",
                    "description": "In questions yet is used to ask whether something expected has happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ........................................ submitted my application.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have they arrived .......................................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The families of the victims are .................................... to get justice.",
                    "description": "Yet is used before a to-infinitive to suggest that something expected has not happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already",
                        "still"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}